tuneclub.com 2009-12-05

# TuneClub

**Privacy Policy for TuneClub.com**

Your privacy is very important to us. In the following we will explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit at this site. This policy applies only to TuneClub’s rules of personally identifiable information collected through our web Site.

Please be advised that because we operate internationally, and certain of our computer systems are currently based in Germany, your personal data will be processed by us from the U.S. to Germany, European Union.

By using the TuneClub Web Site, you consent to any transfer of information outside of your country. You also consent to TuneClub using your personal information to contact you electronically, in writing, or otherwise to provide notices relating to your use of the web Site and to give you information about the products and services offered by TuneClub and its affiliates and mother company. 

If required by law or contract TuneClub may store your information beyond this date.

 **Cookies**

In order to facilitate the best possible experience with our site, we may use “cookies” on our Web Site.

We use cookies to understand site usage of our customers and consequently to constantly enhance the content and offerings on our site. E.g we may use cookies for personalization of your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you when you return to our site). At any time you may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web Site. However, certain areas of our site can be accessed only in conjunction with cookies or similar devices. Please be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might therefore prevent you from accessing some of our content. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features. Unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Web Site, Cookies, by themselves, do not tell your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. However, once you become a Customer and furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

**Data Security**

We have certain electronic, managerial and physical procedures to prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security. However the open nature of Internet communications means, that we cannot guarantee that communications between you and TuneClub will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. 

Visitors of the Website and Customers use the site at their own risk.

**Information Collection – Visitors**

TuneClub might collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Web pages. For example the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 2000 ), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g. America Online) or the type of browser you are using (e.g. Internet Explorer) .

 **Information Collection – Customers**

In order to purchase products or services from TuneClub, we require that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information (please see our Terms & Conditions for additional details). The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at this site include: name, address, e-mail address, cell phone number and MSISDN (mobile station integrated services digital network number), credit card and billing information, download history, customer generated content and/or information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

To fulfill your requests for products and services (e.g., provide you with content via your cell phone), we may share the personally identifiable information you provide with your cell phone service provider or their partner and subcontractor companies. Our privacy policy does not cover such entities use of information. Please consult your providers privacy policy to learn more about its privacy practices. From time to time, we may share personally identifiable information with unrelated third parties to enable them to provide you with opportunities to learn of products or services in which you may be interested. 

We may also disclose aggregated and anonymous user statistics to third parties. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of our Web Site or purchased a particular type of product. 

We may use such personally identifiable information to provide the information or content you have requested (e.g., fulfill your orders for our ringtones, games etc.), to contact you about programs, products, features or services in which we believe you may be interested (such as future promotional materials), or for other purposes disclosed from time to time. We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our Web Site or changes to our Terms & Conditions, privacy notice, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Web Site. In addition, we may use information collected about our users to improve the content and navigation of our Web Site, or for other internal purposes. 

We may supplement the information we collect from you with outside records (e.g., information we obtain from other companies, including wireless providers) to improve our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we consider to be of interest to you. 

In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information collected about you at this site in the following instances: 

Corporate Change: We may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other corporate change respecting the Web Site. 

Legal Action:  
We may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users. We may disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information, when requested by governmental or quasi-governmental authorities conducting an investigation, hearing or the like, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web Site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.

 **Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our Web pages may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors and Customers should consult the other sites’ privacy notices. We have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any updates / changes of this privacy notice shall be effectively immediately and without further notice to you. 

**Questions/Concerns?**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [support@tuneclub.com](mailto:support@tuneclub.com?subject=Privacy).

This notice was updated in April 2007
